http://www.dippindots.com/privacy-policy

Skip to Main Content
Privacy Policy
Welcome to the website ("Site") of Dippin' Dots, LLC ("DDL", "we," "us," or "our").  PLEASE REVIEW THE TERMS OF USE CAREFULLY BEFORE USING OUR SITE.  The privacy concerns of our customers and visitors are important to us.  We are dedicated in attempting to handle your privacy concerns with the amount of care and respect that you would expect.  If you have a need to contact us in regard to our privacy policy or your privacy concerns, please use the following contact information:
DDL Privacy
Director of Corporate Communications
Dippin' Dots, Inc.
5101 Charter Oak Drive
Paducah, Kentucky, 42001
In addition, we can be reached via e-mail at email@dippindots.com or you can reach us by telephone at (270) 443-8994.
Our Information Practices
Due to the variety of opportunities located at DippinDots.com, varying types of information are collected based upon the activity in which a particular user may choose to participate.
Log Data and Cookies.  Generally, all information containing personally identifiable information is provided to DDI on a voluntary basis from you.  However, our servers may automatically detect information such as your IP address, browser type, operating system, page views, or other statistical data (Log Data) related to our Site.  This information generally does not contain personally identifiable information, and this information generally is not linked to any personally identifiable information that you may provide DDI during your visit to our Site.  While we may disclose, sell, or distribute this statistical information about our Site to other parties, the information will not contain any information traceable to a single person or entity.  If for some reason this type of information becomes linked to you in a personally identifiable way, it will be treated as personal information under this policy.
Cookies may also be used by our website.  Cookies will not damage your computer or read information from your hard drive.  Cookies allow certain actions by a user to be remembered by a website.  We do not store any personal information in our cookies, and our cookies are not linked to any personal information stored in our database.  However, you can disable the use of cookies on your computer by changing the preferences of your web browser.
Dippin' Dots Ice Cream Store.  When customers purchase products or merchandise from the Dippin' Dots Ice Cream Store located on our Site, customers are required to provide their full name, billing address, shipping address, e-mail address, credit card or other financial information, and a phone number.  Since we have many repeat customers, you may receive newsletters, sale notifications, or other types of promotions that interest many of our customers.  We do not transfer or sell the information obtained from the Dippin' Dots Ice Cream Store to third parties, except when we have a third party acting as our agent to handle data or functions occurring through DDL.  In this case, the third party will only have access to the information to the extent needed to perform their contracted functions.  These third parties may not use any of your personal information for their own marketing, research or other purposes.
You may concurrently enroll in one of our clubs or newsletters at the time of your purchase.  Our privacy policy with regard to enrolling in these clubs or newsletters is described below.  Since you must be an adult to order products from our site, the Dippin' Dots Ice Cream store registration does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13.  Parents, if you are aware that your child may have provided us with personal information in this regard, please contact us at email@dippindots.com  or the contact information listed above and the information will promptly be removed.
Franchising Opportunities.  In order to facilitate franchising opportunities through Dippin' Dots Franchising (DDF), we need to collect your personal information as well as your financial and business information.  We may disclose your personal information to third parties as part of our consideration in the franchising process.  However, DDI and DDF will not willfully disclose your information to third parties that are not part of our franchise consideration process, and any third party that receives a disclosure of your information may not use the information for their own purposes.  DDL and DDF realize that the information contained on the Dippin' Dots Franchising, LLC. Request for Consideration Form contains sensitive information and will act accordingly to safeguard your information.  However, when you express an interest in obtaining a franchise agreement with DDF, we may internally use your personal information to send you offers of other opportunities that may interest you.  If you would rather not receive information of these offers, please contact us.  Since you must be an adult to participate in our franchise consideration, we do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13.  Parents, if you are aware that your child may have provided us with personal information in this regard, please contact us at email@dippindots.com  or the contact information listed above and the information will promptly be removed.
Electronic Newsletter Subscription.  DDL may from time to time offer a variety of clubs (e.g., Dippin' Dots 40 Below Club) or newsletters in which our customers or visitors may participate. If you register for a club or newsletter and provide us with your personal information, we may use your personal information to contact you and inform you of special offers or promotions.  If you would rather not receive information about special offers, other promotions, or be a member of our club, please contact us.
Contests, Sweepstakes, and Surveys.  DDL may from time to time offer a variety of contests, sweepstakes, or surveys for you.  We may collect your personal information in order to efficiently and effectively administer the contest, sweepstakes, or survey.  Your personal information may be used to contact you in a variety of situations including but not limited to updates on potential changes in the contest, sweepstakes or survey; obtain more information from you; or to notify the contestant winner(s) of their status.  Additionally, your personal information may be used to contact you to notify you of future special offers, promotions, contests, sweepstakes, or surveys with a concurrent enrollment in one of our clubs or newsletters.  Your personal information may be provided to third parties to the extent that the third party is acting as the agent of DDL in administering or handling data regarding special offers, promotions, contests, sweepstakes, or surveys for DDL.  These third parties may not use the information for any of their own purposes.
Security of Data.  DDL would like to assure its customers and visitors that it has taken appropriate measures to ensure that any collected personally identifiable information has been stored securely and will continue to be secure in the future.  We have taken steps such as limiting the people with physical access to our servers as well as including electronic security systems and passwords to protect against unauthorized access.
Amendments to Our Policy.  Please be aware that this privacy policy may be changed at anytime.  You should frequently check this policy and be aware of any changes.
Miscellaneous.  We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that the disclosure is necessary to protect you, our rights, and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or other legal process served on us.
Your California Privacy Rights.
As of January 1, 2005, California Civil Code 1798.83 allows visitors to our Site who are California residents to request certain information and choices pertaining to the disclosure of their personal information to other parties for direct marketing purposes.  To make such a request, please send an email to email@dippindots.com  or write to us:
DDL CA Privacy Rights
Director of Corporate Communications
Dippin' Dots, Inc.
5101 Charter Oak Drive
Paducah, Kentucky, 42001
Questions or Concerns.
If you have any questions or concerns, please send an e-mail with your questions or comments to email@dippindots.com or write to us at:
DDL Privacy
Director of Corporate Communications
Dippin' Dots, Inc.
5101 Charter Oak Drive
Paducah, Kentucky, 42001
You may also telephone us at (270) 443-8994.  (Please have parental permission before calling if you are not 18 years of age or older.)
Children's Privacy Policy
DDL takes great pride in the relationships we have established with our customers.  DDL recognizes the need for additional protection when children provide personally identifiable information online.  Building upon our Privacy Policy/California Privacy Rights, the Children's Privacy Policy of Dippin' Dots, LLC is designed to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA) and other applicable law.  Our information collection practices as applied to children under the age of 13 are described below.  However, we encourage any child under 18 to check with their parent or legal guardian before entering any information on any website, and we would further encourage parents or guardians to discuss with their children the consequences of disclosing any identifying information on the internet.
Information Collected.  DDL prefers not to collect and usually does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.  However, from time to time, we may offer contests, sweepstakes, surveys, clubs, or newsletters in which children under the age of 13 will be required to register in order to participate.  The information we collect from kids during our registration process generally consists of a  first name, initial of the last name, e-mail address, date of birth, zip code, username, and a password.  The birth date is used for age validation for contest or sweepstakes purposes and potentially future internal marketing purposes if enrolled in our clubs or newsletters.  We do not collect any other personally identifiable information from kids during our registration process or require the disclosure of more personal information than is needed to participate in any activity.
Parental Notification.  When a child under the age of 13 has registered at our Site, we will provide an e-mail notifying the parents or guardians of the child's registration within 5 business days.  A parent or guardian has the right to refuse entry into any sweepstakes or contest for a child under the age of 13, and we will delete any stored information about the child from our database after a request by a parent or guardian.  However, if we have not received a refusal of entry by a parent or guardian within 48 hours after a reasonable attempt of notification, we will assume that participation in any sweepstakes or contest is acceptable to the parent or guardian.
Use of Collected Information.  Except for parties contracted to administer online activities, such as but not limited to contests, sweepstakes, or surveys, DDL does not willfully transfer, disclose, or share any information containing the personal identification of children to third parties.  Parties contracted to administer these online activities will have access to the information only to the extent needed to conduct the contest or sweepstakes.  No other use of collected information is allowed by such a third party.  If any artistic representation has been submitted to DDL for posting to our website, the art will only be identified by the username selected by the user unless further consent has been obtained.  The personal information obtained from children may be used in a variety of internal ways.  If the child has enrolled in one of our clubs or newsletters, they may receive periodic updates or special offers.  In addition, the information may be used to contact a child who is a contestant winner or survey participant in order to obtain needed information.
Log Data and Cookies. Generally, all information containing personally identifiable information is provided to DDL on a voluntary basis from you.  However, our servers may automatically detect information such as your IP address, browser type, operating system, page views, or other statistical data (Log Data) related to our Site.  This information generally does not contain personally identifiable information, and this information generally is not linked to any personally identifiable information that you may provide DDL during your visit to our Site.  While we may disclose, sell, or distribute this statistical information about our Site to other parties, the information will not contain any information traceable to a single person or entity.  If for some reason this type of information becomes linked to you in a personally identifiable way, it will be treated as personal information under this policy and will not be disclosed to third parties.
Cookies may also be used by our website.  Cookies will not damage your computer or read information from your hard drive.  Cookies allow certain actions by a user to be remembered by a website.  We do not store any personal information in our cookies, and our cookies are not linked to any personal information stored in our database.  However, you can disable the use of cookies on your computer by changing the preferences of your web browser.
Parental Access of Personally Identifiable Information.  At any time, a parent or guardian may refuse to allow us to collect further information from their child, and the parent or guardian can request that all the information be removed from our database.  You may accomplish this by using any of the contact information disclosed below.
Questions and Concerns.  If you have any questions or concerns, please send an e-mail with your questions or comments to email@dippindots.com or write to us at:
DDL Children's Privacy
Dippin' Dots, Inc.
5101 Charter Oak Drive
Paducah, Kentucky, 42001
You may also telephone us at (270) 443-8994.  (Please have parental permission before calling if you are not 18 years of age or older.)
Effective: June 28, 2007
Opens an external site in a new Window
Opens in a new Window
Opens an external site
